Lesson 24. Amber writes a song. Ted always writes the songs for the rock band, but now Amber
says she wants to start writing songs too. She sings him the first lines of her new song.
Ted, you know how all along you've been in charge of all the lyrics for our band?
That's right Amber. Everybody loves my songs.
Well, I hope they'll love my songs too.
But you don't write songs.
I'm sick and tired of singing your songs all the time. I want to sing my own songs.
Okay, no need to freak out. First things first. Have you written a song yet?
Yes. As a matter of fact, I have.
Well, let's hear it then.
Okay, but it's still a work in progress.
Stop trying to buy time. Let's hear the song.
My boyfriend is crazy. Crazy about baking cookies. I know for sure that there is no cure.
Cut it out. Stop teasing me. I am cured.
All better?
Yes. I'll never bake another cookie again. My parents made a fortune. Now we can all just chill out.